

Shahidullah Software Engineer (Flutter)

My Contact

shahidullah.cse.gub@gmail.com

(+8801631206078

Mirpur DOHS

github.com/Shahidullah191

linkedin.com/in/mshahidullah-044796179/

Skills

- Hands on Experience on Dart and Flutter
- Strong OOP and Designing skills
- Experience with State management libraries (GETX and Provider).
- Working Knowledge of Firebase
- Working Knowledge of RESTful API
- Proficient with Git

Technical Skills

Programming Languages: Dart, C, JAVA

• IDE: Visual Studio, Android Studio

• Database: SQFLite, Firebase

Education Background

- Green University of Bangladesh
 BSc in Computer Science Engineering
 CGPA: 3.68 out of 4.00
 Completed in 2022
- Kalaroa Goverment Collage HSC Group: Science
 Completed in 2018
- K.C.G United High School SSC Group: Science
 Completed in 2016

About Me

Hello, I am Shahidullah. I am a Professional Mobile Application Developer (Dart, Flutter) with 2+ years of experience and a background in Computer Science. I specialize in developing Android and iOS with Flutter Framework with Dart. Intend to build a career in a company in a hi-tech environment with committed & dedicated people, which will help me to realize my potential. Willing to work as a critical player in a challenging and creative environment.

Professional Experience

6amTech | Jr. Software Engineer (Flutter)

July 2023 - Present

Mysoft Heaven (BD) Ltd | Jr. Software Engineer (Flutter)

Feb 2023 - June 2023

Giveturn Tech Expert | Mobile App Designer

July 2022 - Dec 2022

Projects

StackFood: Multi Restaurants	Cont. Development
<u>6amMart - Multivendor Food,</u> <u>Grocery, eCommerce, Parcel</u>	Cont. Development
Integrated Social Protection Management Information System	2024 - 2024
DBID (A2i)	2022 - 2023
ভূ <u>মিসেবা</u> (Land Ministry)	2022 -2023
Online Groceries App	2023 -2023
Covid-19 App Using API	2022 - 2022
Ecommerce App Using API	2022 -2022

Projects

Ecommerce App Using Firebase	2022 - 2022
Newspaper App Using API	2022 - 2022
Weather App Using API	2022 - 2022
Fitness App Using API	2022 – 2022
Music Ecommerce	2022 – 2022
BMI Calculator App	2022 – 2022
<u>Task Management</u>	2022 – 2022

Professional Tranning

BASIS-SEIP T-3 (Apprenticeship) | Mobile Application Developer (Flutter)

2022 - 2022

Responsive Web Design | CodersTrust Bangladesh

2019 - 2020

Achievements

I achieved 3rd semester Dean Award from Green University of Bangladesh.

2019 - 2020

I achieved 4th semester Dean Award from Green University of Bangladesh.

2019 - 2020